SARA ISABEL GARCIA REYES

New York, NY 10128 | 929-259-4488 | sarisgar28@gmail.com <u>GitHub</u> | <u>Blog</u> | <u>Linkedin</u>

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Experience in OOP Ruby on Rails and JavaScript based programming with a background in Finance, Architecture and Design. Possess strong team building and problem solving skills combined with a driven work ethic and desire to constantly learn and expand my knowledge base. Fluent in Spanish and English.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

OOP RUBY, RAILS, JAVASCRIPT, REACT, PYTHON, SQL, POSTGRESql, SINATRA, JSON, HTML, REDUX, CSS, Node.js.

Adobe Photoshop, AutoDesk Revit, AutoCAD

TECHNICAL PROJECTS

Landmark Web-App - GitHub

Review the landmarks you've visited and share with other users.

- CRUD Ruby on Rails web application.
- Ruby on Rails API
- CRUD and RESTful Routes

Cat Matching Game - GitHub

Card matching game featuring cat pictures

- Ruby on Rails API
- ES6 JavaScript

Expense Tracker - GitHub Front-End | GitHub Backend

Budget your personal expenses.

- Ruby on Rails API
- REACT.js and REDUX
- Utilized JSON Web Tokens and localStorage to store encrypted user information client-side.

EXPERIENCE

OhYeah! Influencer's and Brand's Marketing.

Frontend Developer

New York, NY

Oct 2021- Present

- Responsible for developing the product working closely with UX's designer.
- Programming Languages are Next.js, React,js, Postman.JSON and CSS

New York Life Insurance Company

New York, NY

Financial Services Representative

August 2017 - May 2020

- Management of existing professional relationships and development of new, long term business partnerships.
- Analysis of current business objectives and restructuring of goals based on variables including customer feedback, budget forecasting, and procedural improvements.
- Establishment of new clients and investors in a bilingual sales environment both one on one and through large group presentations.

Trade NYC Realty

New York, NY

Realtor

May 2016 - May 2017

• Research and client acquisition based on various renters' preferences in conjunction with market opportunities.

EDUCATION

Flatiron School
Full Stack Web Development, Ruby on Rails, React, Redux and JavaScript program.

New York, NY April 2021

Universidad San Buenaventura

Cali, Colombia

Architecture and Fashion Design with a focus on sustainability, efficiency, and environmental impact.

June 2015